two years ago
两年前
this is the first time
这是第一次
Have lunch with others
与他人共进午餐
I told you before
我之前跟你说过
You don't like to answer me
你不喜欢回答我
I believe
我相信
you do not want to talk to me
你不想跟我说话
I just don't
我就是不
I don't like to talk
我不喜欢说话
i am very talkative
我很健谈
don't hate me
不要恨我
Where are we sitting?
我们坐在哪里？
sit there
坐在那里
There
那里
OK
好的
Haven't said it yet
还没说
What's wrong with Si?
斯怎么了？
Dillon Thomas
狄龙·托马斯
that hair
那头发
I program
我编程
Do I understand?
我能理解吗？
My girlfriend forced me to read it
女朋友逼我读的
you love her
你爱她
she likes it very much
她非常喜欢
she let me see
她让我看看
at the beginning
在一开始的时候
I bought the translated version
我买了翻译版
She said there was no way
她说没办法
she said this poem
她说这首诗
Once translated
一旦翻译
It won't be the original taste
不会是原来的味道
I must watch the original English version
我必须看英文原版
I tell you
我告诉你
I can read a page
我会读一页
I can sleep three people
我可以睡三个人
What's the scariest thing?
最可怕的是什么？
We have been fighting these days
这些天我们一直在战斗
She asked me to write to her
她让我写信给她
After reading
读完后
Didn't he want to kill me?
他不是想杀我吗？
How about that?
那个怎么样？
Is this funny?
这很好笑吗？
Do you agree?
你同意吗？
I cannot agree
我无法同意
if i don't agree
如果我不同意
she is angry with me
她生我的气
After eating this meal
吃完这顿饭后
I will return
我会回来的
come study my poetry
来研究我的诗
I
我
I can't copy online
我无法在线复制
She said she wanted to find a heavy show
她说她想找重节目
I
我
I haven’t written for the college entrance examination yet
我还没有写高考
800 words or more
800字以上
Don't you think this is hard for me?
你不觉得这对我来说很难吗？
How about I help you?
我帮你怎么样？
help me
帮我
how to help me
如何帮助我
Can you make a program?
可以制作一下程序吗？
I have nothing to do in the afternoon
我下午没什么事
i can write to you
我可以写信给你
help me write
帮我写
Have you read this poem?
你读过这首诗吗？
not warm
不温暖
on that beautiful night
在那个美丽的夜晚
Good job Xiangyang
向阳，干得好
. I didn't expect it
。我原本没想到
eat quickly
快点吃
Help me write after dinner
吃完饭帮我写
Xiao Zhou
小周
That's it
就是这样
After discussing with the leader all night,
跟领导讨论了一晚上之后
it has been modified
它已被修改
Partial bidding plan
部分投标方案
In order to avoid any errors
为了不出现任何错误
so
所以
Your workload will increase again
你的工作量又会增加
this is a trick
这是一个诡计
i have to do this
我必须这样做
Work
工作
New auction files sent
新的拍卖文件已发送
It depends on whether the fish can take the bait.
这要看鱼能不能上饵
one stone two bird
一石二鸟
We can avoid leaking standards
我们可以避免泄漏标准
Opponents may be offended
对手可能会被冒犯
at first
起初
normal game
正常比赛
must use them
必须使用它们
in an inappropriate manner
以不恰当的方式
in order to win
为了获得胜利
In the end, I can only punish myself
最后只能惩罚自己
How is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成怎么样了？
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
in a group of animals
在一群动物中
There is a gamer
有一个游戏玩家
Have the electronic tasks been implemented?
电子化任务落实了吗？
Still in touch
仍保持联系
There should be results soon
应该很快就会有结果
This seems to do the job
这似乎可以完成工作
really
确实
no loopholes
没有漏洞
So electronic resources
所以电子资源
this will be of great help
这会有很大的帮助
our own mission
我们自己的使命
should be increased
应该增加
educate him and protect him
教育他并保护他
Don't be impatient
不要心急
Understood
明白了
work done
工作完成了
I gotta go
我要走了
I received your email soon
我很快就收到了你的电子邮件
I am fine
我很好
so i wrote
所以我写了
Thank you, Miss Xiang
谢谢你，向小姐
I help bad students study
我帮助坏学生学习
Thank you so much
非常感谢
You're welcome
不客气
you helped me a lot
你帮了我很多
i must invite you
我必须邀请你
for a big meal
为了一顿大餐
There's no need for that
没必要那样
I know it's around here
我知道在这附近
A popular online burger joint has opened
一家受欢迎的网上汉堡店开业了
do you want to try it
你想尝试一下吗
very delicious
非常美味
Do you want a burger?
你想吃汉堡吗？
I love her very much
我非常爱她
Go quickly
快去
If we are late, we will queue
如果我们迟到了，我们就会排队
Hurry up
快快快
I tell you
我告诉你
The burger is delicious
汉堡很好吃
for you
给你
Looks good
看起来不错
taste
品尝
Thanks
谢谢
Why are you still drinking?
你为什么还喝酒？
I can't drink
我不能喝酒
drink
喝
I will train more
我会多加训练
I really can't
我真的不能
Don't you respect me?
你不尊重我吗？
therefore
因此
drink first
先喝
if you can't
如果你不能
You can give it to me
你可以给我
let's go
我们走吧
Do you really drink?
你真的喝酒吗？
Drink, drink, try
喝喝喝试试
This wine is delicious too
这酒也很好喝
again
再次
I can't comeI can't come
我不能来 我不能来
I can't drink
我不能喝酒
I'll be busy soon
我很快就会很忙
I have to go
我得走了
What's up
什么事
I have a date
我有约会
Is she your sweetheart?
她是你的甜心吗
Why are you in a hurry to go home?
你为什么急着回家？
Turns out there was a date
原来有一个约会
What does your lover do?
你的爱人是做什么的？
Consider playing games
可以考虑玩游戏
from local
来自当地
distance
远方
how do you know her
你怎么认识她的
game
游戏
online love
网上恋爱
Brothers
好兄弟
but i tell you
但我告诉你
This distant love is difficult
这份遥远的爱是很难的
i think it's good
我认为这很好
in fact
事实上
me and my lover
我和我的爱人
We met in the game
我们在游戏中认识了
It’s also a distant love
也是一种遥远的爱
But there is also an advantage
但也有一个好处
This is the separation of marriage
这就是婚姻的分离
every time we meet
每次我们见面
so sweet
如此甜蜜
How long have you known each other?
你们认识多久了？
she is very busy
她很忙
we are usually together
我们通常在一起
we play games
我们玩游戏
Haven't you seen it before?
你们以前没见过吗？
I've never seen him before
我以前从没见过他
you should pay attention
你应该注意
There are many scammers on the Internet now
现在网络上骗子很多
not like that
不像那样
Nothing can deceive her
没有什么可以欺骗她的
Do you have a photo
你有照片吗
Yes
是的
let me see
让我看看
inappropriate inappropriate
不适当 不适当
Who are you
你是
You don’t even have a photo
你连照片都没有
I tell you
我告诉你
Everyone is online now
现在大家都在线了
Which dish killed the pig?
哪道菜杀了猪
Spirit dominates everything
精神主宰一切
no no
不，不
you won't lie to me
你不会对我撒谎
i won't lie to you
我不会对你撒谎
You don’t even have a photo
你连照片都没有
what to fall in love with
爱上什么
Yes, didn't you just say there was?
是的，你刚才不是说有吗
very good
非常好
Just a picture
不过一张图
Nothing can be proven
一切都无法证明
What to do if it’s an online photo
如果是网上照片怎么办
Now many pictures have been deceived
现在很多图都被骗了
There's no way you wouldn't lie to me
不可能你不会骗我
as a friend
作为一个朋友
i must remind you
我必须提醒你
it's falling in love
它正在坠入爱河
It would be best to meet each other
最好能遇见彼此
She is very busy recently
她最近很忙
There will be another chance in the future
以后还有机会
it's time
是时候了
I have to go quickly
我得快点走
Waiter, checkout
服务员，结账
on my account on my account
在我的帐户上，在我的帐户上
go
去
Thanks
谢谢
get a burger
拿一个汉堡
OK
好的
I gotta go
我要走了
I'll send it to you
我发给你看看
This is Xiangyang’s special mission
这是襄阳的特殊使命
sweetheart online
甜心在线
but i usually do
但我通常这样做
with Xiangyang
与襄阳
I found this guy very simple
我发现这个人很简单
He doesn't look like a spy
他看起来不像间谍
so this girl
所以这个女孩
This might be his life
这可能就是他的人生
Sometimes it seems simpler
有时候看起来越简单
Maybe the more you hide
也许你隐藏得越多
don't you think
你不觉得
This girl looks familiar
这妹子有点眼熟
Looks like she's had plastic surgery
看起来像是整容了
besides it
此外它
they are
他们是
they have never met before
他们以前从未见过面
online love
网上恋爱
what girls say
女孩说的话
Xiangyang will believe her
向阳会相信她的
I feel
我感到
This term is called mind control
这个词叫做精神控制下
go check it out
去检查一下
The identity of this girl
这个女孩的身份
Contact Xiangyang
联系向阳
The other party is not clear
对方不清楚
Remember, don't be reckless
记住，不要鲁莽
Don't worry
不用担心
What's wrong? Are you sad?
怎么了？你伤心吗？
No
不
tell me if
告诉我如果
what did you eat today
你今天吃了什么
A burger given by my friend
我朋友送的一个汉堡
Is it tasty?
好吃吗？
very delicious
非常美味
Why am I still unhappy?
为什么我还是不开心？
I said
我说
They haven't met yet
他们还没有见过面
Are you really in love?
你们算真爱吗？
nature
自然
even if we can't meet
即使我们不能见面
but my heart
但我的心
i always think of you
我总是想起你
you are always
你总是
you do not want to see me
你不想见我
of course not
当然不是
one day
有一天
we will meet in reality
我们会在现实中相遇
when?
什么时候？
why are you so anxious
你为什么这么着急
I am not in a hurry
我不着急
I'm just afraid
我只是害怕
I believe
我相信
Now is not the time
现在时机不对
Good time to meet you
认识你的好时机
I don't know you well enough
我还不够了解你
If we meet unexpectedly
如果我们贸然相遇
it will be destroyed
它将被摧毁
our good impression
我们的好印象
besides it
此外它
if you actually
如果你实际上
I'm not as beautiful as in the game
我没有游戏里那么漂亮
if you see me
如果你看到我
you will disappoint me
你会让我失望的
of course not
当然不是
And you
你呢
Will I let you down?
我会让你失望吗？
you always force me
你总是强迫我
you will embarrass me
你会让我感到尴尬
under great pressure
在很大的压力下
no no no
不不不
Don't press
不要按
No need to meet
无需见面
I'm just asking
我只是问问
when we get to know each other
当我们认识彼此的时候
we will meet one day
我们终有一天会见面
I'm waiting for this day
我等待着这一天
I'm looking forward to that day
我期待那一天
let's dance together
让我们一起跳舞
let's go
我们走吧
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
Zicheng
子成
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
I thought you were at home
我以为你在家
Have you eaten?
你吃东西了吗？
I ate before
我吃过
But I can eat more with you
但我可以陪你吃更多
let's eat together
我们一起吃饭吧
where did you go?
你去哪儿？
I asked a girl
我问了一个女孩
No
不
my brother
我的兄弟
Where is Lao Huang?
老黄在哪里？
He gave him a lover
他给了他一个爱人
let me help him
让我帮助他
What were your thoughts when you met that girl?
遇见那个女孩你有什么想法？
not meet people
不与人见面
Just look at the picture and you will know
看看图片就知道了
take it easy
别紧张
I don't check
我不检查
I'm not nervous
我不紧张
Incidentally
顺便一提
I haven’t met Brother Tianyang yet
我还没见过天阳哥哥呢
Do you want to see him?
你想见他吗？
nature
自然
There are many girls in our company
我们公司有很多女孩
i can offer him
我可以向他提供
He is stubborn and boring
他固执又无聊
you don't know him
你不认识他
so shameful
太丢脸了
if you say so
如果你这么说
I want to see more of him
我想多看看他
What
什么
Not suitable
不适合
Why is it inappropriate?
为什么不合适呢？
who knows
谁知道
what if
如果什么
In the name of brother Tianyang
以天阳哥哥的名义
go meet that girl
去见那个女孩
i reveal
我透露
found you
发现你
look at yourself
看看你自己
do not trust me
不相信我
All right
好吧
I'll ask him for an interview now
我现在就请他接受采访
I'll see when he has time
我看看他什么时候有时间
Is Brother Tianyang usually busy?
天阳哥平时忙吗？
what does he do
他做什么的
he is an official
他是一名官员
actually i want to
其实我想
For you
为你
really
确实
I finished
我完成了
waiting for his return
等待他的归来
OK
好的
Do you want pasta?
你想要面食吗？
No
不
follow me
跟我来
where to go
去哪里
I checked the picture
我检查了图片
I didn't find it online
我在网上没有找到
on the Internet
在互联网上
One of them is in his twenties
其中一名二十多岁
In modern society
在现代社会
How could she?
她怎么可以？
any social account
任何社交帐户
There are pictures
还有图片
Yes
是的
In modern society
在现代社会
this is unreasonable
这是不合理的
unless
除非
She lives deep in the forest
她住在森林深处
No network, unable to communicate with the outside world
没有网络，无法与外界沟通
it's out of the question
这是不可能的
If you don't play online games
如果你不玩在线游戏
How could she fall in love with Xiangyang's network?
她怎么会爱上向阳的网络
this is unreasonable
这是不合理的
Is it possible
是否可以
lying about her photo
对她的照片撒谎
in fact
事实上
no such person
没有这样的人
picture
图片
look at his appearance
看看他的外表
Does it sound familiar to you?
你觉得很熟悉吗？
a little
一点
Usually only a few people convert
通常只有少数人皈依
give to someone
给一个人
It will give me a familiar feeling
会给我一种熟悉的感觉
Tianyang
天阳
High-speed Railway Group News
高铁集团新闻
Can translate tonight
今晚可以翻译
OK
好的
I finished
我完成了
I've been working hard during this time
这段时间我很努力
Go home and rest
回家休息
I really want to go home and sleep
我真的要回家睡觉了
Go quickly
快去
Thanks
谢谢
CEO Gao
高总裁
I do not believe
我不相信
That little Zhou is stealing secrets
那个小周正在窃取秘密
How could she?
她怎么可以？
Some things you can only take as facts
有些事你只能当成事实来看
Instead of virtual skin
代替虚拟皮肤
Thank you for your cooperation during this time
感谢您在此期间的配合
we want to thank you
我们要感谢你
Fortunately you discovered this in time
幸好你及时发现了这一点
Otherwise the standards will be leaked
否则标准就会泄露
Where are the actual auction documents?
真正的拍卖文件在哪里？
Translation completed
翻译完成
send
发送
OK, thanks
好的，谢谢
it is my responsibility
这是我的职责
The car you requested has arrived
您要求的专车已抵达
thank you driver
谢谢你，司机
help me
帮我
OK
好的
What movie are we watching?
我们看什么电影？
Have you seen it before?
你以前见过吗？
a new movie
一部新电影
This is it
就是这个
OK
好的
You are ready to receive your package
您可以准备接收包裹
I sent you the address
我把地址发给你了
send
发送
please enter your password
请输入您的密码
The second group and Xiaoyi
第二组和小毅
science
科学
Sent Delivered Delivered
已发送 已交付 已交付
Photo taken
照片已拍摄
this person
这个人
in game
在游戏里
I found the person who contacted Mr. Zhang
我找到了联系张先生的人
everything is the same
一切都是一样的
now we know
现在我们知道了
Zhou Yan and Xiao Ye
周艳和小野
steal
偷
Applicable to high-speed rail train sets
适用于高铁列车组
Auction now
立即拍卖
Not officially started yet
还没有正式开始
they do not know
他们不知道
they got false standards
他们得到了假标准
After the auction ends
拍卖结束后
They will know they were cheated
他们就会知道自己被骗了
Yes
是的
during this period
在这段时期
Except Chu Yan
除了楚炎
She didn't communicate with anyone else
她没有和其他人交流
This person has the ability to achieve v
此人达到 v 的能力
very strong
非常强壮
We dare not
我们不敢
on his phone
在他的手机上
if
如果
before auction ends
拍卖结束前
Haven't contacted him yet
还没联系他
we can catch him
我们可以抓住他
OK
好的
Mr. Chen, I would like to inform you
陈先生，我想通知您
we just knew
我们刚刚知道
That Xiao Yi took advantage of Chu Yan
那个萧毅利用了楚炎
Book online
网上预定
Hot spring hotel room
温泉酒店房间
they are going on vacation
他们要去度假
perhaps
或许
Chu Yan and loneliness
楚炎与孤独
they ask for leave
他们请假
Continue to follow
继续关注
The actions of Chu Yan and Xiao Yi
楚炎和萧毅的动作
Understood
明白了
don't let them escape
不要让他们逃脱
here
这里
very beautiful
很漂亮
The sea here is different from the sky.
这里的海和天海不同。
you can always find it
你总能找到
Such a good place
这么好的地方
She monitors the computer every day
她每天都会监控电脑
you are still tired
你还是很累
let yourself relax
让自己放松一下
at last
最后
rest for few days
休息几天
Let's go to the hot springs
我们去泡温泉吧
OK
好的
I'll go get ready
我去准备一下
What?
什么？
won't tell you
不会告诉你
What will you prepare?
你会准备什么？
let's go together
咱们一起去吧
I also need to prepare
我也需要准备
I also want to prepare
我也想准备
I first
我先
Why is he here?
他怎么会在这里？
We met Xiaoyi
我们遇见了小毅
No chance
没有机会
I'm going to a hot spring hotel to relax
我要去温泉酒店放松一下
I wanna go
我想去
After the case is over
此案结束后
I'll take you there
我会带你去那
take me with you
带我一起走
Really?
真的吗？
really
确实
Invite Huang Ziqing to join us
邀请黄自清和我们一起
Why didn't An Yueqin answer the call?
安悦勤为什么不接？
follow them
跟他们
OK
好的
do something
做某事
This is Leo
这是狮子座
let's go together
咱们一起去吧
Mr. Gao is very generous
高总很大方
I believe
我相信
let's go
我们就走
I'm afraid it will be embarrassing
恐怕会很尴尬
You also know what embarrassment is
你也知道什么是尴尬
I remember the first time
我记得第一次
when you take me to play
当你带我去玩的时候
stand next to me
站在我旁边
like a bodyguard
像保镖一样
I'm afraid others will know
我怕别人知道
You are from the National Security Bureau
你是国安局的
do not laugh
不要笑
Incidentally
顺便一提
Huang Zicheng wants to take Yaoyao away
黄子成要带走瑶瑶
he wants to see me
他想见我
He said we should have dinner together
他说我们应该一起吃晚饭
Did Yaoyao take the initiative?
是瑶瑶主动的吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
Then Huang Zicheng tied up the thread
那黄子成把线绑起来
Huang Ziqing wants
黄子晴想要
to get close to her
为了接近她
he told me before
他之前告诉过我
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
This is Yaoyao
这是瑶瑶
you must be careful
你一定要小心
She is different from Huang Zicheng
她和黄子成不一样
you don't know now
你现在不知道
What does it have to do with Yaoyao?
和瑶瑶有什么关系
in this night fog
在这夜雾之中
if
如果
Use this time to eat
利用这个时间吃饭
check
检查一下
let's see how she is
让我们看看她怎么样
Have you checked Xiaobai?
你查过小白吗？
No
不
They and She Tu had been preparing for a while
他们和佘图准备了一段时间
Verify her account
验证她的帐户
If this person
如果这个人
It is indeed not in Tianhai.
确实不在天海。
difficult
很难
difficult to verify
很难验证
Continue to investigate
继续调查
how's it going
怎么样了
we haven't found it yet
我们还没找到
No
不
I asked about Gao Tianyang's work situation.
我问起高天阳的工作情况。
Huang Zicheng didn’t tell me
黄子成没告诉我
from Duane
来自杜安
He doesn't quite trust you
他不太信任你
Why didn't he tell you?
他为什么不告诉你？
This doesn't prove anything
这并不能证明什么
Incidentally
顺便一提
I'm going to meet Gao Tianyang today
今天我要和高天阳见面
have a meal together
一起吃饭
Huang Ziqing agreed
黄子晴同意了
this is a good chance
这是一个好机会
you can't delay
你不能拖延时间
Know
知道
follow plan
遵循计划
Put everything in the designated place
东西都放在指定的地方
I believe
我相信
You want to know the answer more than I do
你比我更想知道答案
Is this good?
这很好吗？
Latifa
拉提法
I'm waiting
我在等待
couple outfit
情侣装
couple
夫妻
i will give it to you
我会把它给你
OK
好的
let me take a look
让我看一看
very beautiful
很漂亮
give to me
给我吗
i really like it
我真的很喜欢它
love it
爱它
Thanks
谢谢
you came early
你来得早
sit down
坐下
let me introduce you to
让我向您介绍一下
This is my brother Gao Tianyang
这是我哥哥高天阳
This is my dear Yaoyao
这是我亲爱的瑶瑶
My brother Tianyang
我的天阳哥哥
I've been listening to it for a long time
我听了很久了
I was complimenting you
我本来是在夸你
my uncle is very good
我叔叔很好
I just have some doubts
我只是觉得有些疑问
Are you impressed?
你印象深刻吗？
Where is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成在哪里？
I said I invite you here
我说我邀请你来这里
ruin the audience
毁掉观众
It looks like your photo is in your home
看起来你的照片就在你家里
not good
不好
My brother Tianyang
我的天阳哥哥
I heard Zicheng mention you before
我以前听子诚提起过你
I thought you
我以为你
a very serious person
一个非常认真的人
He pretends to be serious
他假装很严肃
this bastard
这个混蛋
Don't be narrow-minded
不要心胸狭隘
Incidentally
顺便一提
I brought a bottle of good wine today
今天我带了一瓶好酒
I forgot in the car
我忘记在车里了
Brother Tianyang, do you usually drink?
天阳哥哥，你平时喝酒吗？
Today is the weekend
今天是周末
I can have two drinks
我可以喝两杯
OK, I'll bring it
好的，我拿来
I gotta go
我要走了
You two talk a little bit
你们两个聊一点
they chatted a little
他们聊了一点
they spoke
他们说话了
I heard Zicheng say
我听子成说
Brother Tianyang is very busy at work
天阳哥工作很忙
our oath
我们的誓言
there are many things
有很多事情
This appears to be a regular employee
这似乎是一名正式员工
no
不是
as i expected
正如我所料
You still have to work overtime
你还得加班
not easy
不容易
Originally this meal
本来这顿饭
I should have called you a long time ago
我早就应该给你打电话了
I do not have time
我没有时间
I've pushed you this far
我已经把你推到这么远了
we shouldn't invite you
我们不应该邀请你
I always hear him talking about you
我总是听到他谈论你
I've wanted to see you for a long time
我想见你很久了
he said a lot about me
他说了很多关于我的事
No
不
tell me you're nice to him
告诉我你对他很好
they grew up together
他们一起长大
when we were young
当我们年轻的时候
You are his scapegoat
你是他的替罪羊
If you are bullied you have to face it
如果你被欺负了，你就必须面对它
He is a good brother no matter what
无论如何他都是一个好兄弟
then i thought
然后我想
I want to see this
我想看这个
legendary good brothers
传说中的好兄弟
in the Legends
传说中
this is the first time
这是第一次
he told me secretly
他偷偷地告诉我
Where do you work
你在哪工作
you are reading
你在阅读
i hear you
我听到你了
I was abroad at the time
我当时在国外
I'm studying in Los Angeles
我在洛杉矶读书
Then stay alone in Tianhai
然后独自留在天海
Is everyone worried?
大家都担心吗？
presentable
体面的
I have a sister at home
我家里有一个妹妹
she always talks about me
她总是谈论我
You have a good relationship
你们关系很好
like
喜欢
Between you and Zicheng
你和子成之间
Is our relationship good?
我们的关系好吗？
look at his words
看看他的话
Mahatsujin
真烦人
Can you bear it?
你能忍受吗？
Me too
我也是
Tenyo brother
天阳兄
I'm going to the bathroom
我去趟洗手间
your tea
你的茶
Thanks
谢谢
Your phone case is nice
你的手机壳不错
Gifted by Yao Yao
姚姚赠送
my brother
我的兄弟
that girl
那个女孩
how's it going
怎么样了
come over
过来
drink tea first
先喝茶
don't give in to me
别屈服于我
about my love
论我的爱
they are all fake
它们都是假的
impossible
不可能的
what is impossible
什么是不可能的
You deceived me with fake photos
你用假照片欺骗了我
really now
真的现在
everyone is there
每个人都在那里
luckily it came true
幸运的是它成真了
Otherwise I will lie to you
不然我会骗你的
If I have a good girl in the future
如果以后我有一个好女孩
Let me introduce it to you again
我再给你介绍一下
Okay, no need
好吧，不需要
How to work
工作如何
This work is very good
这个作品很好
I get up early every day
我每天都早起
It wasn't like this before
以前不是这样的
Didn't you say it yourself?
你自己不是说过吗？
work
上班
I didn't know it worked like this
我不知道它是这样工作的
if you knew
如果你知道的话
I will never go
我绝对不会去
your new friend
你的新朋友
Where are your new friends?
你的新朋友在哪里？
stranger
陌生人
He likes to read English poetry
他喜欢读英文诗歌
are you serious? i'm impressed by him
你是认真的？我对他印象深刻
I like to read some English poetry
我喜欢读一点英语诗
artistic man
艺术男人
i think english poetry
我认为英语诗
very good
非常好
If you have time
如果你有时间
you can learn more
你可以了解更多
and you can improve
并且你可以改进
your cultural skills
你的文化技能
you seem to understand
你似乎明白
Zicheng
子成
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
chatter
喋喋不休
Let’s talk about the history of my brother crying during a blind date
我们聊聊相亲时哥哥落泪的历史
The history of blind dates filled with tears
相亲泪流满面的历史
My brother Tianyang
我的天阳哥哥
Which genre do you like?
你喜欢哪种类型？
let me introduce you to
让我向您介绍一下
I am fine
我很好
i want to be alone
我想一个人呆着
OK
好的
Come on, come on, have a drink
来来来，开酒
Thanks
谢谢
I brought you supper
我给你带了夜宵
I ate before
我吃过
save for something
保存下来做某事
Then keep it
那么就留着吧
When you meet Yaoyao
当你遇见瑶瑶
how do you feel?
你感觉如何？
Uphold the original verdict
维持原判
This girl is definitely not simple
这丫头绝对不简单
At least I don't like it
至少不喜欢
At least
至少
Judging from her words
从她的话来看
i can understand
我能够了解
She always wants to know something
她总是想知道一些事情
especially my job
尤其是我的工作
I left the border not long ago
我不久前离开边境
do you know
你知道吗
I went to Bangkok
我去了曼谷
Know
知道
they are together
他们在一起
long, long ago
很久以前
You didn't say you wanted to see me
你没有说你想见我
suddenly you want to see me
突然你想见见我
Do you think this is a coincidence?
你认为这是巧合吗？
Do I have any doubts?
我有怀疑吗？
You and Huang Zicheng
你和黄子成
With Huang Zicheng
与黄子成
difficult to avoid
很难避免
her doubts
她的疑惑
It's an oversight
是疏忽
I must mention
我必须提一下
You can't say you can always meet me
你不能说你总能遇见我
What do you think of Yaoyao?
你觉得瑶瑶
He knows your identity
他知道你的身份
Huang Zicheng didn't tell her
黄子成没有告诉她
What if I tell her about Ye Wu?
如果我告诉她夜雾的事怎么办？
would be very annoying
会很烦人
So yeah yeah
所以呀呀呀
I'm starting to doubt you
我开始怀疑你
She is with Huang Ziqing
她和黄子晴在一起
Sooner or later her identity will be revealed
她的身份迟早会被揭露
There must be a plan
必须有一个计划
in game
在游戏里
Data in the game account
游戏账号内的数据
have many questions
有很多疑问
OK
好的
snacks for you
给你的零食
Let's go and see
我们去看看吧
Thanks
谢谢
let's go
我们走吧
Why don't you have something to eat before you go?
走之前你不吃点东西吗？
look
看
This player
这位选手
Registered address
注册地址
keep changing
不断变化
new york today
今天纽约
tomorrow is london
明天是伦敦
the day after tomorrow
后天
What proves this?
什么证明了这一点？
this
这
virtual online communication protocol
虚拟在线通讯协议
tasty
可口
Why use
为什么使用
virtual online communication protocol
虚拟在线通讯协议
I don't want it from anyone else
我不想从别人那里得到
find her location
找到她的位置
correct
正确的
and this
还有这个
look
看
It's time to register all her accounts
是时候注册她的所有帐户了
Registration time is Xiangyang
报名时间为襄阳
similar
相似的
When Xiangyang is not online
当向阳不在线时
watch online
在线观看
this game
这个游戏
Specially designed for Xiangyang
专为襄阳设计
correct
正确的
it's the same way
这是同样的方式
Author: Yao Yao Yao Yao
作者：姚姚姚姚
Yes
是的
but it's on the internet
但它在互联网上
She didn't communicate with Xiangyang
她没有和向阳沟通
Because Xiangyang is a tech house
因为襄阳是技术宅
He is different from Huang Ziqing
他和黄子晴不一样
Night fog is like this
夜雾就这样
they will follow
他们将跟随
different personalities
不同的性格
let's find a way to get closer
让我们找到一种方法来靠近
Can we
我们可以吗
Arrive at the line
到线
it depends
这取决于
Huang Ziqing’s abilities
黄子晴的能力
I am coming
我来了
we agreed today
我们今天同意了
I won't let you invite him again
我不会再让你邀请他了
Let's share
一起分享吧
Which stall?
哪个摊位？
trade
交易
I invite you to dinner
我请你吃饭
Have you found your girlfriend?
你发现你女朋友了吗？
I passed
我通过了
This is good
这很好
I didn't expect your lover
我没想到你的爱人
not that smart
没那么聪明
one day
有一天
with your girlfriend
和你女朋友
See who is stupider
看看谁更笨
Didn't I tell you?
我没告诉过你吗？
we haven't met yet
我们还没见过面
Nice to meet you
遇见真好
Let me check it for you
让我帮你查一下
she is very busy
她很忙
you
你
this is not love
这不是爱
our relationship
我们的关系
It's not as complicated as you think
它并不像你想象的那么复杂
Why do I feel this way?
为什么我有这样的感觉？
Your relationship is more complicated
你们的关系比较复杂
It seems like you two are in contact every day
看来你们两个每天都联系
But there are actually many mountains
但实际上有很多山
you
你
they don't feel the warmth
他们感觉不到温暖
this is not love
这不是爱
this is called chatting
这就是所谓的聊天
Do you really not want to?
你真的不想吗？
go see her
去见她
don't worry
别着急
you promised me
你答应过我
Once this period is over
一旦这个时期结束
we will meet again
我们会再见面的
come on bro
拜托，兄弟
it's like being an adult
这就像成年人一样
Let's meet again someday
我们改日再见面
we will never meet
我们永远不会见面
This is nonsense
这是无稽之谈
waiter
服务员
bring the wine
把酒拿来
beer
啤酒
Thanks
谢谢
Come, come, come
来来来
drink
喝
Have you ever thought about it?
你有没有想过？
I only saw pictures
我只看到了图片
Can you rely on him?
你能依靠他吗？
What? What do you mean?
什么？你是什​​么意思？
Have you met that person?
你见过那个人吗？
Now
现在
some people play games
有些人玩游戏
They like to pretend to be women
她们喜欢假装成女人
Actually he is a man
其实他是个男人
uncle
叔叔
noob
小白
It's uncle
是叔叔
it's out of the question
这是不可能的
I am my uncle
我是我叔叔
tell me
告诉我
How are you two doing?
你们两个怎么样？
how to be together
怎样才能在一起
let me have fun
让我玩得开心
online love
网上恋爱
i never thought
我从来没想到
one day
有一天
in a game
在一场比赛中
in game
在游戏里
The scene where we first meet her
我们第一次见到她的场景
I'll never forget
我永远不会忘记